Die, idiot
Die
Bro
he's not telling when
he'll return the money, Bro
It's my habit to pray
before committing a sin
Where's my money, huh?
Daivaji
please let me go!
I'll return your money
Don't kill me
Hey,
do you remember the story
of the cow and the tiger?
In that story,
the tiger gave the cow one chance
I gave you two chances
The principal and interest
together come to twenty-five lakhs
You kept saying you'd pay,
then locked up your house and ran away.
I worked hard to find you
and now you're saying the same thing again
Did you think the tiger would trust you?
Did you think the
tiger would let you live?
Killing someone is a
greater sin than make to kill
I'm sure I'm going to hell
What do you say?
[Chuckles]
Yes, Boss
You laugh when I say
I'm going to hell, huh?
Idiots!
Hey! Janaki
Yes, Boss
Pack it up. Take the money
and send these fools away urgently.
I can't bear to look
at their pathetic faces
Come
I came here because
I couldn't refuse you, Dad
But I won't come inside
Just the thought of seeing that idiot...
You just go and come back quickly
Hmm
Sprinkle turmeric water all over the house
A misfortune worse than
corpse has stepped into this home
How long will you keep up this anger?
I'm your father!
Hey, stop it!
If you say that word again,
I'll rip the nerve out of your throat!
Our Bhanu is getting married
I just wanted to let you know...
Let me know or to insult me?
You shamelessly became
the man of this house twice,
and now you're making him.
I remarried for your sake
can't you understand that?
Ugh... disgusting
You remarried to satisfy your lust,
and now you're pretending
it was to uplift your son?
Disgusting... Look at your pathetic life!
How dare you spit on father!
I'll kill you, scoundrel!
Hey, stop! I said stop!
He is my elder son!
As long as I live, you have to give
him the respect as he is elder brother
Calm down!
How dare to come to my
house and give me a warning?
If you don't step out right now,
two more packed bundles will go out.
Get out!
Come, Dad
Ugh
[Cell phone rings]
[Rap lines]
Hey
whoever did this has completely
destroyed everything!
Hey
the windows, doors, and furniture
everything's been smashed to pieces!
Nothing else is left here, man
What do we do now?
Come, let's ask
Hey, where's the SI?
Where's the pen?
Where's the paper?
- [Cup shatters]
We should file a complaint
Who is the SI here?
Writer is here
The culprits need to be arrested urgently
We need justice
These guys seem to have downed
a couple of pegs more than me
Hey buffalo, come here
Silence!
You three, come here
Hey, he might be the writer. Come
Hmm... let's go
Hey
I think this is the SI
Put the truncheon down
Hi, sir
Hey
what's with that truncheon
and those get-ups?
What's the issue?
Is it wrong for us to
work for our dreams, sir?
We believed in our dreams
and ended up broke, sir
We should not read
someone else's history, sir
Everyone should read our history.
Is that wrong, sir?
Tell us, sir
Hey
I'm holding my head
here with all this nonsense
What exactly happened?
Someone demolished
our company overnight, sir.
Which company?
The Smash Room
Smash it - Destroy it, sir
What?
Is it flour mill?
Do you call such a prestigious
company as a flour mill?
You should be ashamed, sir.
This is the finest...
Oh, you bloody idiot...
What's your name?
Call me Pammu
Pammu...
Pammu... Pappi... Bujji...
Why are you naming dogs?
Tell me your full name.
Gali Parameshwara Rao, sir
That's better, you donkey
What's your name?
Mano, sir.
Full name
Chaganti Bala Subramanya Manohar
And you?
Dulla Ravi, sir
Dula
Dulla
Dulle
You...
What's now?
Someone smashed your shop?
- Sir, sir
Yeah?
It's not a shop, sir... It's a company
Find out who did it
and get us compensation, sir
Ah...
Anything else you want?
You...
First information
then the compensation
My head is going to burst
To ease this headache,
I need a coffee or a good story
Tell me a good story
We come to file a case,
and you ask for a story?
Just tell me
Okay, we'll tell you, sir
Which story do you want to hear?
Your story...
You three are friends, right?
Yes, sir
Since intermediate
And then?
We did BA together, sir
I wanted to start a business
and he pursued photography
- He stayed just like that, sir
Not me, sir... Him
I'm an introvert, sir
Looking at you guys,
I can tell you're a bunch of crazy fellows
Your enemy must have smashed your company
What's up with you, Dula?
Sir, I'm allergic to enemies
If someone talks harshly,
I go cry in a corner
I never fight with anyone
Hmm
What about you, chatterbox?
Sir
2 months and 13 days ago
in the middle of the road,
someone hurled filthy abuses at me
You must have done
something to provoke him
Please hear me out completely, sir
It was during my days working in a DOPIDO
[Phone Rings]
Hello
Good morning, Mr. Gali Parameshwara Rao
We are calling from the
Dopedo Complaint Division
Complaint division, huh?
Then listen,
install mobile toilets
for our Dopedo bikes
It's hard to relieve ourselves
anywhere just like that.
There are CC cameras, you know
Also, lighters for
cigarettes along the way
Sir, sir, sir... We are calling
to talk about the complaints against you.
Against me
Who complained?
Sir, it's reported that
you are smoking during the ride
Just trying to be friendly
with the customer, So what...
And also, you've been verbally
abusing customers as you please
Who said that? Is that black guy,
who rode three days ago
and cheated me out of ten rupees
If I find that rascal...
Why so much anger, sir?
If you speak politely with customers,
you'll get a good rating,
and your incentives will increase
You mean...?
You'll get extra income, sir
Extra income?
How much?
About two to three thousand rupees
Two to three thousand a day means...?
Please hang up the call right now
You should have told me this earlier
From now on, you'll see me
as the most courteous driver ever
Haha... Bye!
Bye, sir. Thank you
I can drink every day with
two to three thousand - [Phone chimes]
The customer is my king!
I'm coming
Why hasn't he come yet?
On TV, they say,
they will arrive instantly
Hey... um...
Hey, stop...
stop...
Take those fish and step aside
What?
Do I look like someone who sells fish?
So?
I booked you
- Me?
Check if you want, 1965
What, were you born then?
Not born, man... OTT
OTT? Is it an OTP?
Yeah...
Correct, sir
Yeah
Please, sir. Take your seat, sir
Oh boy, he knows English too
- Welcome DOPEDO, sir.
- Okay
hold this
What's with the attitude?
No, sir
It's a 5-star rating job
Here, give those watery flowers
Sir, sir, sir...
please take your seat, sir
Don't feel bad... they're fresh fish
The hell with 5-star rating
Sir, will you pay with cash or PhonePe?
I'll give you a fish. Take
it home and ask your wife to make curry
Sir... I'm not married yet
So there's no power in your body, huh?
You're quite the joker, sir
Are you laughing or crying?
Be careful, otherwise we both will die
Maybe this is why they give incentives
Hey, stop... stop
Stop
For what, sir?
There my fish will getting on
Fish?
Yeah, my wife
Stop, man!
They have free buses, right, sir?
Can't you stop where I tell you to stop?
You dirty crab
Come on now
you're walking like a prawn... Get on!
Move
Sir, sir, sir... only one person per ride,
sir It's okay, let's adjust
You can't do that, sir
She knows that way only
The fishes are drying out
You hold the waist
Mine?
Not yours, mine
Just an idea, come on
Hey, not this way, we have to go that way
One-way, sir. We can't go there
It's okay, the SI is our guy
If we go this way, we can go fast
Can't you understand. Just go...
go... go... right, right
Hey, stop
For what, sir?
My small fish is here.
Small fish?
Yes, he is my son. stop!
I can't sir.
I can't means how? Stop.
It's a bike, sir, not a lorry
Stop, man
You talk well
but my kid's frying in the sun
Have some sense
Do you think this is a rural bus service?
Use your brain!
You're the one with no brains
My small fish is getting
roasted in the sun!
Where do you want me to let him sit?
On my head?
On your tank
My tank?
It means, on the bike's tank
Let him sit, why are you staring at me
Hold tight
Hey, stop, stop.
Who else now, sir?
Stop, stop... This is the house
Get down
Hey kid get down
How much is it?
Uh... 58 rupees, sir
Here, I have money in my pocket.
Give it to uncle
Uncle?
Don't want payment?
I want
Here
Go on, why are you staring at him?
Sir, sir, sir
It's 12 rupees short, sir
Do one thing
after the curry is done, eat two pieces
Until then, wait
Sir, sir... Forget that, sir
5-star, sir.
5-star?
There's one in Buddy Complex.
Buy one and chew it
Sir, sir... Not that, sir
5-star rating, sir
Yeah, I'll give it... I'll give it
Now go, go
[Phone notification]
It seems this guy has
given a review on this app
A thousand-rupee fine
for taking the wrong route
A two-thousand-rupee
fine for a triple ride
And for these forty-six rupees earn,
a fine of three thousand
if there's no job, how much does it matter
Oh God!
Sorry, brother
Hey, stop there
Hey
you trash
Wherever you go, I'll catch you
I'll roam every street,
and I'll break your head
From that time,
he might have been following us, sir
With rage and revenge,
he must have smashed our company, sir
Hey, you fool
He either comes, makes a scene, and leaves
or goes home,
has a few drinks, and passes out
There's no way he's chasing you around...
You're not that important
He must be someone else
Correct, Shankar...
He must be someone else - Yes
Hey, get up!
You're just sitting there like a statue
- What's up, Manu?
- Sir
Have you been involved
in any big trouble recently?
Two months and thirteen days back,
Land Mark Hotel's owner gave me
an appointment to hear my business idea.
[Phone Rings]
Hello
How much longer, man?
Sir, I've reached the location
you mentioned... I'm here
What do you see in front?
In front
there's a dosa cart, sir
People are pushing each other for dosas
Do you see a red
towel swinging in front?
Yes, I see it, sir
That's me. Come inside
while pushing those people aside
Land Mark Hotel
is a roadside 'dosa' cart?
Saroj, tell him firmly
- One masala dosa, one egg dosa
how many do you want? One plain dosa?
You stop
Lakshman Rao sir
Ah, I am the Landmark Lakshman Rao
Investor
Phone
Is it you?
Hey, Saroja
come here and take care of this cooking
I'll take a small break
and be there in a minute
Okay. - Sir
- Ah... come my dear.
So, what's your name?
Chaganti Balasubrahmanyam Manohar
Why such a long name like MLA dosa...?
- [Cell phone rings]
[Laughing]
So, what kind of business
are you thinking of doing?
The entire business
plan is in this file, sir
How to do business,
how to expand
Why did you throw it like that, sir?
Then what can I do
If I studied like you,
I would have wore suits and shoes
and I would have roam in cars like you.
If you want, you could travel in a plane,
not just a car, buddy
[Cell phone rings]
See my dear
Check, Whether you have those three things
or not in the business you are talking about.
What are the three things?
First
whether there is demand
in our business or not
like that
Second, whether we are offering
a lower rate than others or not
like me
Third, whether we are
maintaining quality or not
like my tiffins
If these three are good,
we'll raise the flag
Otherwise, your effort and my
money will evaporate like water on a pan
Understood?
That's the matter
[Laughing]
Even, If you hadn't studied
who else would have been
so clever like you, buddy?
Not being literate is the best, buddy
Otherwise
you'll end up begging
Just like those fools
[Cell phone rings]
Lift the call, no problem
Since, he has been trying to contact you.
The one who takes is busy, than who gives
Lift the call and talk
What's going on?
Why did you cut the phone?
Where are you?
A big investor named Landmark Laxman Rao
I am with him.
He is teaching me how to do
business as easy as he made the tiffins.
I am listening.
Okay, when will you come?
The flour on my shirt is getting worse...
I'll talk later
Hello... Mano... Mano...
Is this a joke?
No, sir
Do you think that I would say that
it's a joke only
You are just a dried puris
and stale chutneys seller
And you're talking about how to
do business with a BA passed me
Business is not about three
fingers or a few strands of hair
Business is about demand and supply
You country brute
Hey
you are talking so much
I'll put hot sambar
on your head... sit down
This is a tiffin center
and it's named as Landmark
I will file a case alleging that just
because of eating your tiffins,
dengue and malaria
are spreading in this Area
I'll make your Landmark
disappear on this land
Loss of in shirt
and also loss of car rent
Hey
You're insulting me and my business
You are such an arrogant
How you start your business
how you succeed
I will see
Okay
Tiffin centre Lakshman Rao noted
But
looking at you, it's
not one person
it look like you've fingered
four or five people.
Think again
What's there to think?
How Ammu created such a big
mess in your life. Tell about that
Ammu!
Do you have a girlfriend, man?
Hey Shankar, stop it
Why are you bring up that discussion now?
Hey
if you say anything Ammu,
you will become a beggar
We are not in a better
position than that, man?
So what?
What's wrong with Ammu?
He did everything with her
Hmm.. Looks like there
are some big twists in the story
Tell me
We've been in a relationship for 3 years
Hmmm
Her name is Amrita
Oh, okay
I affectionately call her 'Ammu'
[Balloon popped]
[Music]
"Don't trouble me just like that"
"Don't make me a fool
in the middle of the village"
"Kill me while I still have
breath and don't go with smile."
"Don't bloom as a flower
in the shadow of leaf"
"Don't sing as a bird in the nest"
"Don't block like clouds
spreading the moonlight"
"For hours, days, thousands of lifetimes,"
"For how many years
should I wait like a doll"
"It is better to decide
whether it is yes or no"
"I am not asking you to recite scriptures"
"I am not asking you to churn
the ocean of milk with spoon"
"The help you can do is"
"Only one,
only one, only one, only one..."
"It's just one word,"
"just one word"
"Why are you not telling?"
"It's just one word,"
"just one word"
"Why are you not telling?"
[Music]
"Don't say by not saying writing
letters in the air with your eyes"
"Don't kill me by sending
letters with your smile"
"Stopping everything"
"I came towards you"
"Losing everything"
"One place,
one moment, one voice, one word"
"It's just one word"
"just one word"
"Why are you not telling?"
"It's just one word"
"just one word"
"Why are you not telling?"
Your story is very nice.
Oh
same office
same company
so you'll get plenty
of time to chat, right?
I'm just asking to know
Who are enemies in your stories?
A love story with no enemies?
Not just in this world
it doesn't exist even in the moon also
In each and every love story
the villain is the lover itself
Hey,
tell him the rest of the story
Hey, I told you not to blame Ammu, right?
Actually what's your problem?
It's you only
I've been reminding you for the past month
not to skip this meeting
again, you did it
You never come on time
you never attend the meetings
This time you will definitely
be fired from your job
Let them do it
not an issue
You know I don't like
these kinds of office jobs
So, what happened with
the investors meeting?
Who?
the guy selling dosas on a cycle?
What does he know about being an investor?
He's the one selling dosas
but he has money
He has money?
Even if he gives it to me, I don't want it
I'll find another investor
- That's it
- See
this is your problem
arrogance
Since college days
You've been running
around with business ideas
but you haven't even caught one investor
If it's not business
you can focus properly on your job, right?
For the past three years
same 20 thousand salary
No job
no business
Don't you trust me?
I'm trying to make you
understand the situation
My family members
bringing up marriage proposals from US-UK
but I am avoiding them
It's only because I trust
you that I've been waiting
Our manager,
Vamsi, he is getting 2 lakhs salary
and he has been chasing
me for the past two years
Even I am managing all this shit
I'm doing it for you
How longer should I wait?
Oh...
Are you threatening me
with the options you have?
Then why did you drag this
20 thousand salary job for so long,
when you could have settled
with that 2 lakh guy?
What do you mean by that?
I completely understand now
You need one person to fall in love
but to marry, you need someone
who earns lakhs or crores,
right?
Mano
- Bro... cigarette
How much do you need
One Crore or Two crores?
In six months, I'll start a business,
become successful, and come to you
Then decide
if you want the crore guy or the lakh guy
Why did you call?
Huh...
You called me Koti
Huh... Come here, man
Why are you calling HR like that?
I'm quitting the job, that's why
- So?
Go tell that manager
to shove it
Hah
There is a full intense in
your story like Arjun Reddy's story
Ok
That guy put some ice in his pocket
And what have you done, huh?
He picked up rice, man
Hey Shankar, If he gets into a fight with
such a nice girl, Instead of saying
"Oh, no,"
what's that supposed to mean?
It's a waste to tell you a love story
Hey
let's not get involved
in his personal matters
You continue, go ahead
Forget about love and all that,
I've firmly decided
to focus on my career, Sir.
What's this, resigning from your job and
coming home... Have you lost your mind?
That's why they say decisions
shouldn't be made in anger
Ammu said it for your own good, right?
And you went and fought with her!
Why don't you care about me?
You always take her side
That "Pammu" is better than you
Whoa!
Who's that guy lighting
dhoop sticks in afternoon?
Hey, you dried-up twig
that's not fire smoke;
it's cigarette smoke
He's been smoking since he got here
What happened, man?
What else?
He fought again
Shut up
She insulted me, man
She said I don't have money
and can't settle
These girls are
all like chameleons
always changing colors
You're not wrong for fighting
I told you right?
He is better than you
With a single friend like you
the whole group would be doomed
Do you even know what he did?
And you're saying "thanks"?
I don't know
He got mad at the pond
and dried his butt in the sun.
He got mad at Ammu
and resigned from his job
If not a pond, we'll go wash in the sea.
It's not a big deal
Dude
When did you resign
11... 11:30
Super, dude!
Wait a minute
Just like that... Don't worry
Cheers!
For what?
I resigned at the same time, too
Super sync, Dude
Hey, hey, hey
What's wrong with you two cursed idiots?
Hey!
Who needs that jobs?
I've got a head full of business ideas
Don't start again, man
Amrutha needs to know my worth
I need to start a business
and make money
That's it, we're fixed
From today,
we three are business partners
He's Tata, you're Birla, and I'm...
You're Laila. Don't drag me into this mess
I'll do my job;
you two do whatever you want
Hey, you act like a big wild photographer
All you shoot are mucus in kid's noses
Hey! If you insult my profession...
I will hit with this bottle
Okay... Cool
Here take it
No, I don't need it
Okay, I respect your decision
Then go
Cheers!
Ugh, idiots
From tomorrow onwards,
you'll be beg for food.
Hey
How do you know his phone lock?
Not only his phone lock
I know his entire history
and his boss's history too
For only one peg, he spills everything
If we do business,
all three of us have to do it together.
This is friendship!
Calling Srikanth sir...
Hello
Tell me, Ravi
I'll kick you with my shoe
Hey,
who are you?
Ravi's inner self
Hey
While you're strutting around
Bangalore with your mistress
our guy is managing everything
here without your family knowing
Hey
He can't keep your dirt inside anymore.
He's dying inside
Hey!
Hey! Does that black Padma need a car?
How lusty are you?
Hey!
He's spilling everything to everyone
Not only spilling,
He is printing pamphlets
about the entire matter
and distributing them all over the city?
I'll fire that idiot immediately
Are you going to fire him?
He is firing you as his boss
Give him the phone first
Oh
You want to hear it from him directly?
Okay
Ravi
Hey
I don't want it.
How many times should I tell you?
Don't ask again about it
Ok
Have you heard?
You should be ashamed
As a human being you
should have some wisdom
Don't you feel shame,
he is saying no every time
Give him the phone once
OK
You want to listen in his own words.
Ok
Ravi
Srikanth sir is on the line
Sir?
Why is he calling me at this time?
Sir
Ravi is here
Hello, sir
I'll come on time tomorrow
and take everything, sir
Take what?
I'm firing you from the job
Take whatever you want
Sir, sir, sir
Listen, sir
Sir listen...
I'll do a great job
What happened, Dude?
He called just now
and said he fired me, dude
Sync, dude, sync
This is destiny written
by the creator for us to sync up
Fine... But now what should I do,
if he fired me all of sudden?
Move from the pond to the sea
You mean business?
Yes
You're Tata
you're Birla
and I'm Ambani
Cheers!
So finally,
you've dragged me into this too, huh?
Hey, what business are we planning to do?
Hey!
If Mano is here
there's definitely a plan
Let's gather some money first
I'll go home and bring ten
[Pammu laughing]
Very cheap
If I say ten, my dad will throw me out
I'll bring at least fifteen
I'll bring twenty-five
Twenty-five?
It's my saved-up money.
I don't need to ask anyone for it
If I want to do something,
I just go ahead and do it. That's it
Hey dude
We have to prove that, we're
not just village dogs; we're roaring lions
Come on
let's go to village
and come with full of bags
Alright... I'll meet you later
What's with him all of a sudden
Can't you even make a phone call?
Give me the bag
Why is the bag empty?
I'll fill it up when I'm leaving
What are you filling it with... stones?
No, lakhs of rupees
Lakhs?
I need ten lakhs, Dad
For what?
To settle solidly in life
Hey!
It looks like the things
we discussed last night
reached him
We have saved a lot inside
Go and Bring them
This girl Lakshmi
from Nuzividu
They're offering 12 lakhs
and a 3/4-acre of land
When I say I want to settle in life,
I don't mean by getting married
I mean by doing business and succeeding
What's gotten into your head
Instead of getting a proper job
you're talking about business
Salaries won't change lives, Dad
If you try things you can't handle
you'll burn your hands, son
[Bellows]
Where's our Idiot
Early in the morning,
he brought his empty bag
he watched into the cattle
pen and went outside. Useless fellow.
You're always suspicious about him
He must've gone to meet his friends
Hold on, hold on
And you gave birth to such a boy
My son is here now
Come, come
Please
- Get down
Yeah coming
This is my dairy farm
This is like my home
This village is a very green city
Mom, bring two tea
That's my dad
Hey, you stop.
After the deal is finished
Something is fishy
I will buy two beers
This village beers
one beer equals to four beers, very strong
Okay, okay
Presently,
I'm talking about these buffaloes
Listen very carefully, okay?
Don't repeat
This one is Cutie
[Bellows]
she gives six litres of milk a day
This one is Naughty,
she gives eight litres
And over there is Sweetie
[Bellows]
If she's in a good mood,
she can give up to ten litres!
As long as the milk flow is good,
it's fine
If it's a buffalo,
it'll definitely give good milk
Just don't dilute it with water.
Tell us the price carefully
So, if you invest three
lakhs in a buffalo now.
all three together for ten lakhs
[Gasps]
Isn't it nine lakhs for all three?
GST... Buffalo Service Tax
newly launched!
Please reconsider the price
Look, customers
buffaloes don't come free
If you want, take photos of my buffaloes
and compare them in the next shed
Buy them wherever you find cheaper ones
There's no bargaining on the buffaloes
Ugh, you keep quiet
Alright, boy
how much do you want as advance?
I don't like these advance
payments or credit card transactions
Single payment, single settlement
Hey, my dear stupid, son?
- Dad!
What's going on here?
I'm making a deal to sell the
buffaloes and start a business, Dad
From now on, milking
lifting dung
no need to do all these things
Just rest in peace
You want to sell my buffaloes
and start a business?
Come on, Dad
When a father's property
belongs to the son,
the father's buffaloes
also belong to the son, right?
You silly dad
You should've at least told me, son.
Are you building an
AMB Mall or something, Dad?
Why disturb you for just three buffaloes?
Lazy fellow!
You're selling my buffaloes...
My buffaloes!
Stop it now
Dad, don't hit me. No manhandling
Let's sit and talk
Hey!
What's there to talk about with you?
Did you feed them?
Did you lift the dung?
Did you feed them water?
Did you milk it?
Hey!
What right do you have
to sell my buffaloes?
Where are you going, huh?
Stop right there!
Wait a minute...
- So, are you selling the buffaloes or not?
So, you want sell the buffaloes?
We will pay in single payment
- You came to buy them?
It's not him
I should beat you guys first.
Scowling faces of yours...
Ugly faces of yours... Hey!
What's your problem with them?
You shut your mouth
You're useless
Sorry, Dad
I didn't realize you
loved the buffaloes so much
Forgive me, Dad
Yes!
If you don't mind
let's sell four acres
out of the ten near the lake
You...!
Hey...
Finally, you guys brought it
I'm opening it now
Hey!
Why are you opening mine first?
Open his
Okay
Open his first
Who gave the plan? Open his first
The one who promised to bring fifteen
open that one
The one who committed first!
Hey! Leave my hand
Bull shit!
Ah, Why is there nothing in this?
Hey!
there's no money in it!
I had a doubt about
you right from the start
Dude, even you couldn't manage it
Both of us are in sync, huh?
Ugh
Stop it, man
When a brainless guy goes to the market,
a useless guy team up with him
In this moment,
you and your useless hugs...
That's not it, bro
The situation didn't cooperate,
nature didn't support us
Your miserable luck
Hey...
You said you have 25, right?
Let's start with that
Good idea, bro
I knew you'd rely on me.
That's why I withdrew and kept aside
Take this
Twenty-five thousand!
Not lakhs?
So you guys planned to bring lakhs?
What kind of business can
we start with twenty-five thousand?
Ugh!
We trusted you, man
Now what? Let's sit near the
check post and sell mosquito bats
Hey, shut up!
I'm better than you guys.
At least I brought some savings
You made stupid challenges,
saying you'd nail it and smash it,
but you came back swinging empty bag
Hey!
Only those with guts make challenges, dude
Hey! you're spoiling
him by saying like this shit
Hey, Mano
Mano,
have you finally realized
what our capacity is?
Ammu wanted to tell you this many times
but every time, you kept arguing
What's done is done
however we failed in life
At least get succeed in love
Go and apologize to her
Apologize?
You want him to hold her feet?
You want to destroy the pride
of manhood by holding her feet?
Hey dude!
He is not that type of
man who hold the feet, bro
He's fire
You're dead today
Stop there!
Oh my god.
Stop there you fool.
Stop
Because of you only, he became like this.
[Claps]
Happy birthday...
Many more happy returns of the day to you
Sir
sir
please
Sir
Okay
Happy birthday, sir.
Call me Vamsi, baby
Why the formality of "sir"?
Do you have any problem?
No... It's okay
No problem
Okay
Mano
You said you were allergic to cigarettes
and now you're saying it's okay,
no problem
Oh, right
the smoke from a
twenty-thousand rupee earner
and the smoke from a two-lakh rupee
earner are different, aren't they?
I forgot
What is it?
Are you here to fight with me again?
I thought maybe you were thinking about me
but I was wrong
In just two days, you forgot me
and got so close to him
that you're calling him "baby"?
You're great
Do you even understand what you're saying?
Hey Mano
chill bro
Let's enjoy the party.
Shut up, you Kerala coconut shell face
Aren't you ashamed to try
on someone else's girlfriend?
Showing off your two-lakh salary, huh?
Once I succeed in business,
I'll give two lakhs to a peon!
You sit down quietly, or else
that coconut shell of yours will break
Mano
behave yourself!
Amrutha, look at him
he's overacting now
He's crossed the line
Do you know what they call me in Kerala?
Singamale!
And you think you can mess with me?
I'll smash you to pieces, you fool
Who's scoundrel? Your scoundrel, huh?
Mano, stop this!
You're pushing me away?
Fine... Break-up
Really...
was it truly a breakup?
I've stopped thinking about her, sir
The reason I'm telling you all this is...
because I cursed that manager, right?
I'm doubting if he personally
targeted me because of that
Could be, man
as your story is progressing,
troublemakers are getting involved
Hey, Giri
- Yes, sir
Come here
- Why is there no Nellore in this?
- Sir
Go to the address they mentioned
find out exactly what happened, and
come back with a full inquiry report.
Go on
- Ok, sir
Continue, Mano
A new character has entered the story, sir
Thank you
Earlier, you said something, right?
Could you say it again?
Let's live the best lives
Not that one
the one before that.
Oh yeah
If we don't work for our dreams
we'll have to work
for someone else's dreams
That's it. Very good
What a line!
Ah
it's been so long since I've seen
young people fighting for their dreams
Excellent, brother!
Dream
Dream big
and make those dreams come true
Take our country to new heights!
If given a chance,
we'll take up in a lift too
Who are you?
I am Magnet Manikyam
I unearth the gems hidden in the soil
Do you work with soil?
It's not labor work, man
You can tell by my clothes, right?
I find determined young people like you
and help them
Tell me, brothers,
what do you need?
One chilli chicken, sir
Anything else?
Nothing else, sir. Just make it
a little spicier; it's not that satisfying
Nothing satisfies you
Anyway, earlier I mentioned
gems in the soil, and he is that soil
Just ignore him
My dear diamonds
tell me...
What do you want? What help do you need?
We need investment to start a business
Saying it isn't enough
Be clear
We need money
Perfect
You've met the right
person at the right time
My dear Khaleesi
Oh wow
Come, my dear lady.
Guys
this is Ritu
my current, ex, future girlfriend
Hi!
- Hi!
Sir, sir...
You asked what we wanted, right?
Now there's no chance for you.
You sit down
If you want anything with all your heart,
the whole universe
conspires to get it for you
Wow! What a line
I didn't understand anything
other than "poori," sir.
It's not "poori chapati," man
If we strongly desire something
the entire universe conspires
to make it happen
Why would the universe conspire, sir?
Not a conspiracy
It's a quote
You've read those books
with pictures, right?
Oh, those picture books, sir?
Ritu.
Let's go
I'll take care of the investment.
Tonight, dream big
not just any dreams, but productive ones
And in the morning
Ritu
Shit!
See,
if this guy doesn't tear it up the address
come by that address
Why are you in such a drought, man?
Come on, Ritu
Take care
Bye
Come to my dreams
I'll take off my shoe and smack you,
you dirt-brain
Daivaji Nilayam
Hey
This place looks like a haunted house,
and they've named it Daivaji Nilayam!
Hey
I think he's coming
Is it he?
Yeah. He is the one.
Look, that's my Ritu also there
Wow
you've come to the right address,
and you've come at the right time too
Great time sense
Isn't this your house, sir?
No, no! This isn't my house
My house is much better than this
This is our investor's house
I'm just the middleman between you two
You still haven't changed, huh?
Go wash your hands
That means he gives the money,
I convince him
I just take a 20% commission
in the middle, that's all
So you're not the one investing the money?
No, he is.
So, he is a broker?
Hey!
Negotiator
Mediator
or equalizer
There are better words like this,
you know.
Just like you leave your shoes
outside before entering a temple
it's better to leave
him outside before going in
Only then will good things happen
Sir, sir
Hey, stay calm
Sir
take whatever commission you need,
but just give us the money
So, how much money do you need?
You know, just one or two
Around fifty lakhs, sir
Fifty... fifty lakhs?
That's a huge amount!
How much security can you offer?
That's the thing
While the father was begging,
the son came and asked for biryani.
If we had that, why would we come to you?
Fifty lakhs, not fifty thousand
I thought you had time sense,
but it seems you lack common sense
You need to provide some kind of security
Weren't you the one who said
if you wish for something strongly, the
whole world conspires to make it happen?
Just do some conspiracy yourself
Even conspiracies need security!
Fifty lakhs? It won't work for me
I can't do it
Maggie
Hey, stay calm
Okay, fine
I'll manage it
Follow me
You're doing this for me, right?
I said follow me!
Was it about them that
you spoke last night?
Yes, bro
these guys are very sharp
Persistence
Effort
Determination
Edie
Ameen
Check them
What's happening?
I am sure they will pass the check.
Open your eyes
Take your breath
Open your mouth
Open
What is this?
Water
Healthy fat
Oh,
this guy is touching somewhere
Sensitive parts
Okay, boss
Get the cash
Sir,
What's with this checking?
Daivaji won't give a single
penny to the sick or the weak
it's his "Health is Wealth" policy
You guys are healthy, right?
Tone it down
Janaki
Does he call his wife to hand him a knife?
He never got married
He called his assistant
Is she looks beautiful...?
Yes... She is so beautiful.
She suits you Perfect
Is he really an assistant?
Doesn't look like it
Take your rage out on
him... He's the right one for it
Give your Aadhar cards...
Sign and take the money
What's with the signature, bro?
Yeah
Can't you even sign?
No collateral, at least sign the papers
Oh, your signatures must be legendary
What do you even have to offer
as collateral other than bad luck?
Tsk... remove your hand
Is there any problem?
They are asking,
Why do we need to sign, bro?
If you don't pay on time
We'll send you abroad
Abroad?
Daivaji owns a lot of companies in abroad
If you don't repay the loan, they
send you there and make you work for free
to pay off the debt
But you won't need that, right?
You will work hard for one
year and repay the total amount.
You're sharp guys, right?
Except for this one
Hey, I had a doubt all along
Bro... One minute
Hey, come here
What are you thinking?
It's a win-win for us
If we don't pay, we get a free trip abroad
Both sides are sweet deals.
What if they send us abroad and
make us clean toilets or wash dishes?
Who would do that, man...? Damn
Even if they do, it's okay for me.
Batting? Bowling?
Fielding
I'll slap you with my shoe
What's the delay, man?
Why are you stalling?
My left eye is twitching
Hey
When good fortune comes
body parts will shiver
It's scientifically proven
I don't understand the delay
There's already another
party waiting outside
They'll sign
Are you guys okay with this or not?
Nope
So, what now
Will you sign or not?
Don't worry... I'll make them sign
Thanks
Here, take it
Thanks a lot, sir
Told you before, you're the best
Bye, sir...
Enjoy
Come on, bro... Let's hit the first bar
Crazy boys
Your story is really crazy!
Did you actually start a business?
Even though I started with a unique idea
it's a universal business, sir
[Music]
What about all these items,
it looks like a flea market
Tell me in the way that I could understand
How much BP can damage a person's body,
you know, right, sir?
I know
If you hold on to that
anger for more than 10 minutes
you'll lose your emotional balance
If you hold that anger in
your body for more than half an hour
it will damage your two kidneys
If it's all day long
it can lead to brain stroke or paralysis
You remember what the elders used to say,
right, sir?
One's anger is their own enemy
That's why,
Anger should be resolved immediately
Correct
That's why we have our Smash Room
If you're angry with someone,
just take them there,
let them imagine the person,
and smash things up
Decide whether you want to keep the anger
in your body or maintain peace of mind
that's how
we started, sir
[Music]
"Don't control control control"
"Don't control control, man"
"Your frustration,
irritation, whatever it is"
"Don't control control, man"
"If you suppress your anger,
it leads to more rage"
"Your heart might explode, boom boom"
"Troubles, losses, pain, so many forms"
"If you keep quiet,
you'll end up exploding"
"Beat your crazy rage to the rock."
"Beating until you're drained,
hitting and hitting"
"Nobody will ask you, break something"
"Hit"
"Hit, hit, hit, hit"
[Music]
"On your birthday"
"even if it's a dry day"
"Even if your secret chat is out"
"watching your wife"
"Even if you're kicked
out of the World Cup again"
"No one will say anything"
"we can't stay just watch"
"Your whole body's on fire, burning"
"Without cooling down"
"you'll keep yelling"
"A stroke might come,
you'll be knocked out"
"Beat your crazy rage to the rock."
"Beating until you're drained,
hitting and hitting"
"Nobody will ask you, break something"
"Hit"
"Hit, hit, hit, hit"
[Music]
"Even if your girlfriend
breaks up with you"
"Even if you clash with your boss"
"Even if you have a
problem with your friend"
"We can't curse them, we can't slap them"
"Your blood will boil, everytime"
"Your blood pressure will rise, you won't
be happy Life is just one, after all"
"Beat your crazy rage to the rock"
"Beating until you're drained,
hitting and hitting"
"Nobody will ask you, break something"
"Hit"
"Hit, hit, hit, hit"
"Washing machine"
"Beer bottles"
"Hit"
"Tables, chairs"
"Hit, hit, hit, hit"
"Tube lights"
"Hit"
"Any tire, fridge,
smash it Smash, beat it, bash it"
"Hit, hit, hit"
"Dude, what about the coconut?"
"Just break something, man!"
Hey,
do you know what big
mistake you three made?
You did business on people's anger
and now it backfired on you
The people who came to you
lost control of their anger
and started smashing things
They went home and they beat their wives
Their wives are all come together
and they destroyed your company.
that's the story
Sir
now we know who did it, right?
Please file a complaint against
them and give us compensation
Compensation?
You guys are the ones
who did that reckless business
and now you're asking for compensation?
If you file a case,
no money will come, fool.
Sir
I just told you such a big story for you
please do something for us, sir.
Alright, do you have
any insurance or anything?
Shankar, who gave you the police job?
If you had one, why would we come to you?
Perfect
Definitely you will lose this case
You guys stick to your 9
to 5 job and leave all this behind
Sir, please, don't say that, sir...
please sir
I have a friend in Hi-Tech City
I'll tell him to get you any job
just leave me alone
Please
Sir, sir, sir
- Hey, Shit
What's with this guy?
I get tense
Hey, how are you guys drinking
even in this much tension, man?
It's not just a little, man...
it's fifty lakhs! - [Cell phone rings]
And five lakhs interest... From where are
we going to get that and pay it back, man?
Who the hell is going to give
us money right now? - Magnet, dude
Hey, what kind of unlucky
mouth do you have?
Ugh!
Hey silent!
Hello
What's up?
I heard your smash room got smashed?
We were just about to call and tell you
If you arrange the interest this time,
we'll manage it ourselves next time
Why should I arrange, man?
I'm just a broker
You got ten lakhs as commission, right?
Hey!
Screaming
You took ten lakhs as commission, right?
Can't you at least help us out a little?
The way you're screaming means
it looks like it's time
for you to leave the country
Ok then
Now go pack your bags. See you soon, man
That thief.
Hey, where are we going
to get fifty lakhs now?
Forget fifty lakhs, who'll trust
us and even give us fifty thousand, man?
Hey, dude
I've got a super idea!
If you say anything about business,
I'll push you and thrash you right here
No, man
not that
Recently, I saw a guy on YouTube who said
he was getting married and asked for funds
He collected over four and a half crores!
Hey, that's all fake, man
Hey, it's not fake, man! I even woke
up in the middle of the night to check it
Hey, in his drunken stupor,
what are he pulling out from his lower
Your phone?
See
[Mobile video playing]
He got it because he has subscribers, man.
Who would give it to us?
We have friends, right?
Let's make a video asking for help.
That's called begging, man
What are you going to pull out now?
This is not begging
This is crowd funding
Follow me
I will prove. [Snaps fingers]
[Crying]
Hi friends
Our Ravi friends
Yes, friends
Today, the reason we
have come before you is
to share the sorrow we are facing, friends
Our Ravi,
who is a friend to all of you
he has
cancer, friends
Yes friends!
[Friends crying]
He doesn't have many days
left on this Earth, friends
There isn't a temple we haven't prayed at
nor a hospital we haven't visited
Every gynecologist has given up, friends
saying they cannot do anything for him
By luck
one doctor
one gynecologist specialist, Dr. Daivaji
has said that if we can arrange
fifty lakhs, Ravi can be saved, friends
Fifty lakhs is beyond
our capacity, friends
If all of you give a helping hand
Ravi will be saved
and stay with us, friends
Yes, friends
We've provided two numbers below, friends
Please send your contributions
through PhonePe or Google Pay, friends
Hey, did you give my number?
Friends
if you kindly donate
once I recover, I will account for
every rupee and return it to you, friends
Please, friends
Hey, shut up, Ravi
stop and come here
Okay, man
Go fast man
[Phone chimes]
Monsingh!
I won't open it until it hits 100.
Hey!
[Laughs]
Hey, you useless idiot! What's with
all this shouting early in the morning?
Hey! You said, it wouldn't work out!
when I revealed the night plan, right?
Yeah!
Look how the charity plan worked out!
I got 100 messages
Oh!
This loser only got three messages
What, man?
Nonsense
He got just one threat message
It's so funny
Stop overreacting and tell
us how much the fund raised
Fine
First, let's see this
loser's pathetic messages
Subbarao
one rupee
My uncle
What a shame!
Chenchayya, two rupees
Uncle
Yes!
Ugh
Srikanth sir
He usually sends a lot
How much?
Fifty paisa
Ugh!
Even charging this
phone also waste of time
What kind of friends do you have?
Hey!
Enough with your nonsense. Open yours now
You open it yourself
Now, having money in the
account means we should pay taxes
Hey, these are all voice messages!
Really?
Play them
Hey, idiot!
Send back the three thousand
rupees you took from me
otherwise I'll break your face!
Next, next
What should I send you, man?
you waste fellow?
You're not even worth a quarter of a rupee
Next
Yeah, I'll send
Come and...
Hey,
no time now. Next!
To get rid of your bad luck
contact immediately
Shri Renuka Ellamma Astrologer
Hey, save this one!
I'll kill you!
Hey, you idiot!
Check the video before
you send it, you fool
Who asked you to return the money, huh?
Who told you to speak
up in the middle, anyway?
We could arrange meals at Annavaram temple
I thought, it will add some emotion
to your words. So I told this, bro!
What emotion is there in this?
He's talking about returning it.
First, he doesn't even have the money
to repay the person who gave the loan!
Who's the idiot edited this video?
I told him to cut it, bro.
He didn't cut it
If I didn't cut it,
don't you know to check before posting?
Maybe I forgot because of work tension
Your so-called "work" is
just drinking like a leech, right?
You guys brought us back to square one
The plan is ruined now
So what if we missed
one message in that mess?
Oh! Ok.
Ammu, sent thirty thousand dude
I told you no?
You guys didn't believe Ammu was good
Correct, bro.
I realized it I unnecessarily sent it
to everyone, including this person
Lost my dignity
Hey, hey
Oh no
What are you doing, man?
Hey! Don't send
Ugh!
He lost his brain
In this miserable situation,
do we really need these outbursts?
Where are you going
to get five lakhs to pay?
One idiot supports another idiot.
[Doorbell rings]
Who could it be at this time?
Go and check.
Nobody is here, huh?
Hey!
[Snaps fingers]
Oh... Jhansi Sir
Not Jhansi, idiot
Janaki
Yeah, that's what I meant
Did he came for interest payments?
Come
Come fast, man!
Brother asking you to come quickly.
I mean, we are kind of busy...
maybe for five or six months
You'll be in deep trouble, you rascals
If you don't show up in ten minutes
I'll crush you!
Hey,
I'm scared, man
Just say I have a fever
or something and manage it
- Hey!
- Come
Dude, I'm also not feeling well
Don't act like a school kid, man
No, man.
Daivaji bro
happy birthday! Bro.
Wishing you 500 more birthdays like this
You're investing just 100
rupees but expecting 500 feasts?
Thanks bro.
- Birthday, huh?
Go
Will he invite us to a party?
Happy birthday, bro!
Here.
This short fellow.
He kept saying bro is
calling and scared us like this
Hey, I still have my doubts, man
He seems to be in a good mood
Maybe he'll forget
about the interest we owe
Greedy fellow
Let's approach him with guest
body language, not debtor body language
let's go wish him
Guest body language, huh?
Let's handle him with this garland
Hey
Go away
Why don't you shave atleast today, Pushpa?
Bro, happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, bro!
Bro... Wish you a happy married life!
Hey! Dude?
Sorry, bro
We don't know it was your birthday
otherwise,
we would have brought a poem or a song
Forget poems and songs
Did you bring the interest money?
Oh no! He hasn't forgotten... He remembers
Why are you all looking so pale?
Today is the deadline
for the interest, isn't it?
Well, bro
There's a small problem
Next month
We'll pay everything
Should I cut
Should I cut or will you?
Business took a hit, bro
I have sharpened this knife, bro
One clean cut will do the job
Calm down, Jamuna
Let it be
It's not Jamuna
it's Jaanaki!
Bro, why are you even
discussing with them?
No time for this
one cut and done
Bro
this is unfair
If we don't pay interest,
will you cut off our heads?
He's talking about a goat's
head for biryani, not yours
For biryani
Now go get it
Go
I'll crush you, scoundrel
You
I warned you if you don't pay interest,
I'll send you abroad
But
bro, we don't even have passports
They'll sort out your
passports and send you off
Bro
just send us off
We can't handle these
tensions and businesses anymore
By the way, which country will you send
us to - London, America, or Switzerland?
Somalia
Somalia?
Where's that, bro?
It's not in India
Then it's foreign, right?
Dude, wait... You doesn't know anything
So
What do we do after going there?
That magnet guy didn't
tell you the whole story.
He's having food at a feast there
Go and ask him
I'm the king
He is enjoying here
and these are my loyal clients.
Hey Magnet
who's this guy threatening
to send people to Somalia?
Somalia, Mongolia, Uganda,
or Karkanda... he'll send you anywhere man
Those are foreign lands too, right?
He says we don't even need a passport.
Passport, Aadhaar card not necessary.
They just stuff bodies with
smuggled goods and toss them onto ships
Bodies?
Of course
this is the original business of Daivaji
Hey...
you call us 'sharp as knives'
and 'gems in the dirt,'
but you're running such a big conspiracy!
I told you before,
even conspiracies need security
You said no security, no deal
and this dumb brain didn't even get that
You think I'm running
a charity with no security?
Hey, you clay-faced fool
I even thought of loving you!
if you talk about Ritu,
I'll slap you with my slipper
What's this... who are you talking to?
Not you... him
Hey
what will you do, huh? What will you do?
What will you do?
I thought of giving my life for it
Who are you to give life for her?
Cool down
Who let this guy in here?
Daivaji is already killing someone else
Why are you standing
there with a grim face?
Tell me why you came here.
Today is your birthday, right?
I came to see you for that
Also, Bhanu's wedding is fixed
so I came to give you
this wedding invitation first
You came here just to taunt
me in front of everyone, didn't you?
Just to humiliate me because I haven't
gotten married even after fifty years
Get lost
Why do you have so much anger toward me?
What did I do?
You really don't know what you did?
Alright then
Do you want to reveal
your past in front of everyone?
Fine
Everyone, listen. [Claps]
When I was thirteen
my mother passed away
A year later,
I was bedridden with some terrible fever
and spent a month in the hospital
[Coughs]
Hey! Drink some water
Then
Do you know what did
this lusty Kameshwar Rao do?
What is this, Dad?
I have brought you a mother, son.
She will take good care of you.
You brought me a mother?
Or Did you bring a doll for you?
Son
- Ugh, go away
Go away
If you marry just for your son
Will you give a birth
to another child within a year.
Not within a year
it'll be five years before he's born.
You're misunderstanding everything
You did all the mistakes,
and you are saying that it's all my fault?
Go
Go away
Sir, sir, sir
Sir
Nothing's happened to him!
He's just playing tricks, pretending
Throw him out
- No sir
No sir
- Hey Janaki
It looks like he's had a heart attack
What happened with that sheep race story?
Hey, come, hold him
- Let's take him to hospital
What should I do?
Without even considering his own father,
he just started yelling at everyone like that
Hey
think about our situation first
Still, all that's on my mind is Somalia
Hey
I'm leaving
Where are you going? You think you
can escape leaving us stuck in this mess?
If your business is at a loss
what's it got to do with me?
So, you and I have nothing
to do with each other?
Hey, at this time, stop
Who are all these people?
- Mom nothing's wrong with Dad
- Bhanu
He was fine till yesterday, right? - He
will be fine, Mom. Don't worry about Dad
He will be fine, Mom
Don't worry about Dad
Sit down
[Crying]
Nothing's wrong with him
Just a minute
You were the ones who brought my Dad here
- Yes, Sir
Thank you
What did the doctor say?
He said it was a massive heart attack
We'll know in 24 hours
Without telling me,
he went to the his home for the first time
What happened there?
He yelled at him in front of everyone
and was pushed away
What a disgrace
I'll tear that guy into pieces
Bro
[Enjoying]
Hey, Mano
Bro
I didn't understand, sir
Did that old man die?
The treatment is still going on inside
What treatment?
We brought all the garland, Band
Complete the ritual
Hey, You scoundrel
- Bhanu stop it
Are you a son to a father?
You
You humiliated Dad in front of everyone
I won't leave you.
Bhanu
What will you do? What will you do?
Bhanu, the doctor is coming
Stay here, Rascal
- Go. Go
Doctor, how is Dad?
I'm sorry
we tried our best. He is no more
[Gasps]
Bhanu
- Bhanu! [Crying]
- Mom
Bhanu
Doctor
Once more
He has passed away
Hey
Aa-ha
very pleasure to ears
Lusty Kameshwar Rao
born in
died in
You Idiot
He died
because of you he died
No, you killed him
After my father's funeral,
if I don't kill you
I'll change my name
What name will you take?
Bhanu
Mom fell down here
- Doctor
- Mom
Go... Looks like your
mom also has a ticket
Hey
- Hey, let her get on the bus
- Bhanu
Mom
What happened doctor?
Suddenly, her BP dropped
She needs to be shifted
to the room immediately
Mom
- Hey, Mano
- Brother
Come here
Brother
That old man's death day,
my birth day both are same.
I'm double happy today
You asked for some time
to pay the money, right?
I'm giving it to you now
Thanks, brother
Next month,
we'll give you the two interests together.
There's no time, my friend
- Janaki
- Brother
How much time will it take
to burn that old man's body?
Tomorrow's new moon day, right?
It could be done day after tomorrow
Aah! You have that time.
You need to pay both the interests now
Otherwise
I'll send you three people
to Somalia
Hey Play the band
[Drums beating]
Our father's gone
You need to save us
from this problem, Ritu
You have to do something
If needed,
I will put this garland around your neck
Ugh, no way
What do you mean by "no way"?
You and your skull face
We will throw you and
him in jail for deceiving us.
No use
Did you forgot that you
have signed on those documents?
That Daivaji will never let you go
Don't speak so harshly, Ritu
Leave that guy aside
Think about our future
Please, Ritu
- Leave me.
After my father's funeral,
if I don't kill you.
I'll change my name
How much time do you think
it will take to burn that Old man?
Tomorrow is a new moon day
It could happen the day after tomorrow
That much time you have for all that
Ritu.. Ritu.. Please
- Hey leave
Hey.. There's no need to beg anyone...
We'll pay off the entire debt in two days
Hey move aside
How's that possible..?
When it's Mano
there's always a plan, buddy
Come.
Hey, what's the plan then..?
Keep it a secret...
One day, I'll make you pay for it
[Phone Ringing]
Hello...
Hey,
Your father
Do you want him?
Hey,
who are you?
My father passed away, man
Your dead, father only?
Do you want him?
Hey hey,
what are you talking about, man..?
Get clarity in five
minutes and then call me
Hello, hello
Doctor...
How could you be so careless?
What will you tell them?
Sorry, sir.
Doctor.
where is my father's body?
After completing the formalities,
we sent it to the mortuary.
You can take the body after that
Doctor
tell me the truth
what happened?
Where is the body?
Sorry, sir.
The body has gone missing
Gone missing?
Yes, sir...
your father's body has gone missing
We have also filed a police complaint
You idiots!
Hey Man
has the clarity come?
Hey,
who are you?
You Scoundrel
What did you do to my father's body?
Hey,
what's with this corpse wagon? What
are these clothes? What's going on here?
Daivaji gave us two days
Bhanu's father's last rites
are supposed to happen on the same day
So?
What's the need for last rites?
Logs, incense sticks... about 100 people.
Ah, those will be there
But the body won't be
But body
Why won't the body be there?
We are taking it, that's why
Hey
are you out of your mind?
Kidnapping a dead body?
It's not kidnapping
it's called ransom
Handsome
It's not handsome, you idiot,
it's ransom
In Telugu...
Returning their stuff back to them
Oh
So, if we delay
we'll get all the money we need
Okay
Hey
what if we get caught?
They'll come after us
Hey, in this short time,
do you have any better idea? Tell me
Hmm.
Presently, no
Bhanu really loved his father,
you know that
He'll definitely pay the money
We'll take that money
and give it to Daivaji.
Problem solved.
Don't worry.
We'll get the body in 5 minutes.
"You need to hustle and bustle"
"For your life"
"Nobody will back down here"
"It is for money"
Hey!
You guys stay here
Take care. If anyone comes
Are you asking us to run away?
Hey
You stay here
You go inside
If anyone comes, we'll give you a signal
You stay quiet and act normal
Hey, what happened?
I stick a Doll to the
stretcher of the old man corpse
Instead of Bringing the body, why did
you sticked the doll to the stretcher?
It's for identification
It should be recognizable
It will be
The body is coming
Is this Komarayya's body?
Yes, yes, it's mine.
Sign here.
Ok You can take it
This isn't it. Stand
This is not it either
Kamaleshwar Rao's body
Yes, yes, it's ours
Is it yours?. Ok Sign here
Take it.
- Thank you.
Wait, let's check it later.
Listen carefully to what I'm saying
For the funeral to happen
you need your father's body
and to get your father's body
we need fifty lakhs
Fifty lakhs?
Yes
Fifty lakhs only
bring it to the specified
place at the given time
First, send me a photo of my father
Ha
you want proof?
Not just a photo
I'll send a full HD video
Send it, Rascal... send it
[Laughing]
Ravi
Sing a good song
[Enjoying]
I need you...
[TV News] 'Until now, kidnappers only
targeted children and girls'
'Now, they aren't even
sparing the dead bodies'
'Ugh!'
'It's shameful to even speak of it'
'Through your media'
'I want to give the kidnappers
their first and final warning'
'No matter how big criminals you are'
'within 24 hours, you all better
come forward and surrender yourselves'
We just brought the body,
how did the police find out so soon?
They are giving a warning
If not,
Oh no... oh no
I will shoot you on sight
Hey
I'm applying for shoot at sight orders too
By evening, the deal will be completed
don't worry, don't make me worry
I am getting tensed
Hey
Pammu
you record the video
I will slowly open the zipper
Whose?
It's the corpse
Ugh
Hey!
You record the video
come ahead
zoom in full HD
Hey...
"You need to hustle and bustle"
"For your life"
The body has changed
Who is this girl?
Where's the old man's corpse?
Hey, hey, hey
Do you think keeping it
in the fridge is the right thing?
Do you have a better idea
to avoid body odor?
The fridge is definitely the best option
Open the door, man. It's heavy
Oh.. oh.. sorry
Push it
Push it inside
For making friends with people like you,
I also Watch out for the leg, man
Oh no no no
What are you guys doing?
We put the body inside so that it can cool
Hey! That's my hard-earned fridge!
And you're putting a body inside it?
If we leave it outside,
it will smell, dude
If you want,
keep your water bottle on the top rack
Oh, come on!
You all can die your way. I'm leaving!
- Hey, hey, hey...
How can you leave in the middle like this?
We three started this together, right?
Listen to me.
What's left to listen to?
You said it's a business
I said ok
You said let's take the body
my foolish mind agreed to that too
Now we have no money to give to Daivaji,
and no body to give to Bhanu
You Idiots
And God knows who took away
the old man's corpse.
On top of that, the cop keeps giving us
warning after warning
How are we going to escape
from all these messes?
That's not it, man
Shut up! I'll kill you
Hey, let's come up with a plan
Do you think Daivaji will
let you go if you leave now?
Do You forgot that he has
all three of our Aadhar cards?
If we escape,
he'll definitely target our families
Just kill me now
Hey
why are you getting so tense?
The corpse is chilling nicely inside.
There are three of us here,
we'll come up with thirty ideas.
At least one of them should work, right?
It's your dumb ideas that got
us into this mess in the first place
Hey
when Mano's here, there's a plan
Daivaji already gave us two days of time
So that's not a problem
Bhanu doesn't even know who we are
so that's also not a problem
And the CI?
For the police to solve a crime scene,
it'll take ages
Right now,
the point isn't Daivaji, Bhanu, or the CI
The real issue is how that
body will go missing from there
What happened?
According to my plan
there are two things we need to do
First, we must get rid
of the corpse which is inside
Second,
we need to find out
where the old man's body is.
There's a third thing too
We need to gather the courage
to lie down after drinking some beers
Hey. Move aside, man
Hey
Search the whole house, guys
Don't leave a single corner unchecked
Hey... What are you guys doing?
Your Stupid,
worth no more than a quarter bottle.
I'll bury you in the ground
Hey! Put him down...
Put him down!
What's up, man?
Hey
where's dad?
He's gone, right?
[Hiccups]
Did he somehow come back to life?
Hey
Bhanu
we searched the entire house...
The body isn't here
The body... is missing?
[Hiccups]
Hey
just got a doubt
since we didn't find the body here,
that's why
That girl took it to the extreme
Remember this
this time,
even dad isn't alive to save you
The maiden arrived with pot in her hand
Did you see how he is suffering
because of the old man death? Idiot
I want to see him crying his whole life
I want to see.
That old man's body should
never get a proper funeral
Peace to the departed.
and Peace of mind to the one who is alive.
Two cannot be found.
I must find that old
man's body before he does
Ugh... What is this?
I am scared much,
even the alcohol isn't hitting me, man.
Forget that. Whose body is it, anyway?
It's one of those unclaimed bodies.
Hey
it's an unclaimed body, right?
Let's just hand it
over to the Nirvana folks.
Why should we go through the
hassle of disposing of it somewhere?
Hey, idiot
if we take the body and hand it over as an
unclaimed one, they might get suspicious
and they will call the police.
Then the cops...
[Door creaks]
What?
How is that opened?
If the skull didn't burnt completely
the spirit of the body
might come after us, they say
Is it true, dude?
Oh, stop it
When we put the body inside,
we might not shut the door properly
That's all
[Doorbell rings]
If the corpse is there,
why does the sound come from here?
What's going on?
Hey, I'm telling you,
it's definitely the spirit
A spirit ringing the doorbell?
Come on, don't start with your nonsense
No, man, it's not that. Hey
Why are you staring like that?
Is it a spirit?
It's worse than that, man
The one who held the press meet
CI!
CI, huh?
Oh no!
It's all over now
Total destruction
I told you I didn't want to get involved,
but you two dragged me into this
Hey, stop panicking.
We don't even know why he's here
You guys said,
"The cops won't do anything"
Let's manage this calmly
Dude, watching his fear
is making me nervous too
You open the door
Whatever happens, let's deal with it
Pammu
- Um...
The body's in the fridge
You're the one who got us into this mess
Over here
Bachelors, huh?
Yes, sir
How did they let bachelors
stay in a family apartment?
We are also family, sir
But They are in village.
Oh!
Looks like there's
a good beer party going on
What's the occasion?
It's.. sir.. it's a native tradition called
Atlataddi. Actually, inside the body...
not "inside the body," sir!
He meant, we had a couple of
beers to ease the pain in our bodies.
That's what he's saying, sir
It's true sir
It's nothing
Just frustration over some business losses
We just had beers sir
That too only one beer sir.
Just like that
to drown our sorrows
This isn't sorrow
it's fear
Now see
So, alcohol, huh?
Yes, sir
Alcohol? Cigarettes? Or
something worse,
like weed or country liquor?
Oh no, sir.
We don't have those habits
Then why are you folding hands like that?
Why did you put your hands there?
Why did you put your hands back there?
Where else should we keep them, sir?
Why are you shouting?
Sir, not like that sir.
When a CI comes home,
we get tense, right?
How do you know I'm a CI?
He just said it now, sir.
Oh!
Actually, sir
we saw you on TV
You look better in person than on TV.
[Laughing]
It seems like all the
drunkenness has gone down.
Chill, bros
I feel like drinking too
Can I have a beer?
Why just one, sir? Have three!
[Gasps]
Sir, all the beers are outside
Why do you have such a big
fridge but keep the beers outside?
It's... ah...
An egg broke this morning,
and it smells bad in there.
So we kept beers outside.
- Really bad smell, sir
Bad smell, sir
Don't bother checking the smell
Just enjoy the warm beer, sir.
Alright, why don't you guys join me?
No, sir
you're our guest
Cheers!
He's drinking all the beers, man.
Beers
lack of cooling makes it hit faster
I'm already tipsy
Oh...
Sir... sir...
Hey,
A new family moved into the flat next door
Why wouldn't I know, sir?
I tried talking to
the girl when they moved in
She's so arrogant, sir
Hey! You idiot
She's my niece. A girl like
her should have that much pride
Our niece, sir?
So, you came for that?
They're not at home
I called, but no response
Since you're next door,
I thought you might have some information
While I was here, I had a beer
[Laughing]
- Good decision, sir
Shut up
Next time
If I ever hear that any
of you so much as look at her
I'll break bottles on
Ah! Catch...
Sure, sir
Give it
Give
- Take it, sir
Hold my hand
Why are you bringing that?
- How would I know, man?
When you don't know something,
just keep quiet
Lullaby, lullaby
go to sleep, baby.
Hey, loose-tongued fools
Who tells the cops someone
flirted with a girl?
That's why we found out why he came
Let it go. He's gone now
Did you see how scary he was?
[Doorbell rings]
- Oh, my God
This sound perfectly syncs
with the situation here, man
Who's it now?
Who knows?
Is it him again?
We're doomed, man
He must've gotten suspicious
That's why I said not to open
the fridge door, but you didn't listen
Keep it down, man
Whether he saw it or not is a later issue.
Don't shout
He must've definitely
figured out about the body
Let's see, man
Hey!
If you are silent, I will open the door.
What's the matter, sir?
sir...
Sir... sir... Sir...
He's heading toward the fridge.
Do something, man
Hey, do something and stop him!
Hey
Why are you lifting a rod?
To attack me?
Manage him
Prank, sir
Yes, sir
Does I look like an innocent person
who is unaware of which is prank
or which is an attack?
Tell me
You've done something, haven't you?
Why isn't my niece answering her phone?
What did you do to her?
The phone must be on silent, sir
We didn't do anything, sir.
Should I beat you up to death,
or will you confess?
That's it, sir.
We really don't know anything, sir.
Hey, I've been saying from the
start that we shouldn't take such risks
but you didn't listen.
You dragged me into this
What risk?
Sir, he's just drunk and rambling, sir.
He doesn't know anything
Shut up
What risk?
Will you tell me? or should I shoot you?
Sir,
sir, he's just drunk, sir
He doesn't know anything, sir.
- In the fridge...
What's in the fridge?
In the fridge...
a body
What are you doing?
A body in the fridge?
I don't know anything, sir
To keep it cool, sir.
You guys, accidentally took
a different body
from the hospital instead of the old man's
Yes, sir
[Laughing]
Who's going to believe that?
Should I explain it in a believable way?
You three found a figure, used her
got her pregnant
She made a fuss
So, you guys killed her
Then you stuffed her in the fridge
No, sir...
We're not that kind of people, sir.
We're telling the truth, sir.
Hey
- Sir... sir
Do you know what made me
so angry that I wanted to kill you?
you told me that Someone's offering
50 lakhs for an old man's dead body
It's true, sir
What true? Who, who is offering?
His son, sir... Bhanu, sir.
Who is that Bhanu?
Bhanu?
Yes, sir
Liquor Bhanu?
Yes, sir, he is the one
Call him
Sir?
Call him!
Speaker... Put it on speaker
Speaker.
[Cell phone rings]
That scoundrel only
Talk, talk
Hey!
Why did you switched off your phone?
I told you to send the photo
The 50 lakhs you asked for is ready
Mute...
Ask for a crore
Sir...?
Ask for a crore, you idiot
One crore rupees
The body rate has changed...
Not 50, it's a crore
What?
One crore
I'll give you the crore you asked for
Send the photo
It's coming
You guys are something else
You've caught a rich guy
Do you know
He is also standing
in the elections this time
If the news comes out now
that his father's corpse is missing
where would he hide his face?
We made a mistake asking for just a crore
we should've asked for more
Damn!
Let's split it 50-50
until then keep the phone switched off
Sir
Without the body,
how do we handle this, sir?
For a crore, it's a small issue
I'll take care of the body
Just don't forget to switch off the phone, understood?
Be in that job
Sir, what about the body in the fridge?
What's the big deal?
I'll carry that corpse myself
and dump it with some unclaimed bodies
Super, sir
Thank you, sir
You idiots
would you get 50 free
See
I'll account for every 50 you take
You handle the figure body
I'll take care of the father's body,
got it?
Okay, sir.
Need any more clarity?
Let me know, no problem
No sir
Move a side
Ugh! Where did we start,
and where are we going, man?
Why did all of this happen to us?
I never expected he'd
give us a twist like this
He gave a solid build-up as a sincere
officer at that press meet, didn't he?
This is how all the sincere people
end up like this only. - [Doorbell rings]
Damn it! Who the hell invented this bell?
Remove it first
He's torturing us in installments, man
Hey! Hey!
Let it go, man
- What are you doing, man?
If I hit him, he should go into a coma
Even we don't have money to buy
single curry, he talking about one crore.
Hey!
Hey Stop!
We can't handle another murder, man.
What's with this rod?
That... some pest of a pig keeps
ringing the bell and irritating us.
We were in the process
of getting rid of it
I lifted it
If you mentioned the fridge...
Come
Tell her too about the body in the fridge.
You bloody idiot Damn it!
If you fail in business
is this how you sit around
drinking beers and smoking cigarettes?
Why did you come here?
Ugh! Damn it!
For this...
Many more happy returns of the day
It's your birthday, man
- Happy Birthday, man
It's my fault, Mano
When you were running around for business
I fought with you over office
meetings and wedding pressures
I've always been allergic to that manager
why did I compare you to him?
I wanted to come earlier
but my project kept me busy
Come, cut the cake
Are you still mad at me?
I'm not in a happy mood
to celebrate a birthday
I'm under a lot of tension
Everyone has tensions and pressures
My project leader Mandakini
has been missing for three days
Her phone is switched off
and her room is locked
The clients keep calling
I'm dying because I can't manage
Everyone's life is like this only
So, what now
Your business has gone bankrupt
so what?
Just get another job
You said someone is missing. Who?
Mandakini
Do you have her photo?
Yeah...
See
What happened?
Have you seen her anywhere?
No, no! Why would we see her?
Nope, not at all
No, Ammu
Poor girl
She's such a nice person
She's like my close friend
No idea what suddenly happened to her
Anyway,
first cut the cake
Happy Birthday to you...
- Ammu, get up
- What? Get up - To Where?
To home.
Without cutting the cake
First cut the cake
The cake isn't going anywhere.
We can cut it later
Happy Birthday to you
If you stay in this bachelor's room any
longer, the neighbours may misunderstand
I'll come and meet you later
We'll talk then
That's not it
- Meet you later. Bye
What's with him?
Why did he suddenly act like that?
Oh, man! What did you do?
If she finds out we stuffed
her friend's body in the fridge,
she won't even want to see our faces
Mom...
How are you now?
Now I am better, dear...
Where is he?
We should light a lamp near his head?
Mom... Dad's body is still at the hospital
The formalities aren't complete yet
Are you making arrangements
for the last rites?
Today is New Moon Day, right?
The priest said it shouldn't be done today
He said if we do it before
sunset tomorrow, it'll be fine
He left without even seeing your wedding
Because of his elder son's words
He spent his entire life struggling.
Imagine how tormented his soul must be
- Bhanu
- Mom
Make sure there are no
shortcomings in his final rites
Ok mom
Conduct them properly and respectfully
Shivanna...
Yes, Bhanu?
- Brother...
How could you just
leave Dad's body like that?
When I was at the hospital with Mom,
what were you doing?
Even I agree to give money,
he is not responding
Now his phone is switched off
Who is he?
Where is my Dad's body?
Now I'm using the perfume on
you I reserve only for Valentine's Day
just imagine how much
respect I have for you, uncle!
Settling in Goa is my dream,
and today that dream
is coming true because of you
So, the whole credit goes to you.
Hello
all that credit should go to me
not to that body.
Oh, you're so silly!
How can someone who can't
even breathe take credit?
That's why I am giving to him
Now
who overtook their plan and
made sure this body came to us first?
He?
It was you, right?
So, the whole credit goes to you
[Music]
I'm tired of telling every other
random guy to "work hard for your dreams."
Trusting this broker work won't
even get us a shell on the beach in Goa
at least we can't buy small piece in beach
Let me show you what
negotiation really means
[Snaps finger] Yes
[Cell phone rings]
Hello
I have a five-foot-long, two-foot-wide,
80-kg aromatic Mysore Pak here. Want some?
Hey
wrong number... hang up the phone
Hey Bhanu Bhanu...
Liquor Bhanu, this is the right number...
Yeah
who are you..?
I don't know how much
you need to know who I am
but you definitely
need the Mysore Pak I have
With love, Mysore Pak.
Dad...
- with love, Mysore Pak...
do you have my dad's body corpse..?
Sharp!
If you are this sharp
you can easily make
a crore and a half ready
Go ahead and make it ready
Hey, you worthless jerk...
stop with these dramas
Yesterday you said a crore...
now you're saying a crore and a half...
Yesterday it was an LKG call
now it's an OG call...
I'll send you a photo, enjoy the festival
Send it
Uncle, smile
- [Camera clicks]
This Amor Hospital, right?
The Punjagutta branch...
Yes, sir
In that hospital
there is mortuary
I need the CCTV footage related to
that mortuary for the entire day yesterday
Okay, sir
Talk to the hospital...
This is a bit urgent - [Phone rings]
Definitely sir
Do whatever it takes
Hello
CI sir.
Who's this?
This is Liquor Bhanu speaking.
Liquor Bhanu..?
Yeah... One minute.
Sir.
- You go and take care of that task
Okay, sir. Okay
- It's urgent
Hello
What I am about to tell you
must remain between us
Sure, go ahead
Out of the two bodies that went missing
yesterday morning from Amour Hospital
one is my father's
Oh... is it...?
He passed away yesterday
morning due to a heart attack
Oh no
I'm so sorry to hear that
The person who took my father's body
is demanding 1.5 crores to give it back
1.5 crores?
It's one crore...
Did you say 1 or 1.5 crores?
Yes, I'm telling you, 1.5 crores
Yes, got it
He even sent me my father's photos
The one
who sent you your father's photos
is the one demanding 1.5 crores
right?
Yes, exactly
Ah... okay...
Paying the money and
retrieving my father's body
is not a big deal for me
but I feel like killing those people who
are using a dead body to play such dramas
Exactly... exactly...
Who he is?
Where he lives?
Can you find out?
That's not a big issue, sir
Technically, what we will do is...
tap your phone
When his call comes in,
you just need to make sure
the call doesn't get
cut off for 30 seconds
That's it
You must've seen this in many movies
it's so easy.
We'll handle it... no problem
Okay
Bloody scoundrels
[Cell phone rings]
Sir... a call is coming through, sir.
Yes... connect it
Hello
Did you see it? Your Mysore Pak...
Do you believe me now?
I believe you
Then what are you waiting for?
Get the one and a half crores ready
It's ready
Do you want cash or a cheque
or an online transfer?
You rascal!
Why did you cut the call
when I was giving the address?
There's a chance the call could be traced
we need to stay safe.
Oh Ritu...
just missed it!
How are you this sharp?
I never believed in 'beauty with brains.'
I want a baby with you
Call now
OK
Sir... it's coming again
Connect it... connect it
Hey
why did you cut the call
without saying anything?
Because I feel like it
I am OG!
I'll tell and then hang up,
or I'll call without telling.
If you shout, I'll increase
the amount by half a crore
Fine
tell me now at least
Hmm
Exactly at 2 o'clock
in the JRC cellar
Bring the money and take the body
It's a grand exchange fair
How should I recognize you?
In your dreams
Tell me how
Hello
Baby
Cheers
Hello
My son cut the call
within 30 seconds, twice
It's clear
that he's watching movies
Its' ok
Don't worry
we know the address, right?
We'll catch him
How will you catch him?
My team and I will go there early
in plain clothes and wait
You
just follow my instructions
Okay?
Alright
[Cell phone rings]
Hello
Where are you, huh?
Hey
who is this guy, talking without respect?
Hey,
who are you,
talking like this without respect?
You
Hey, hey.
I'm CI Vishwaroopam speaking
Oh, man... Crazy...
Ah... Sir, sir, sir
Sorry, sir
Tell me, sir
You didn't save my number
Save it
Okay, sir... We'll do it, sir
Where are you?
We are going to the hospital, sir
Why the hospital?
Sir
It's
The body went missing, right, sir?
So
We're going to recreate the scene
to figure out how it went missing, sir
Hey, hey... you fools...
Listen to me
First, stop the vehicle, stop it
Man, it's really hard to talk to this guy
You talk to him
Sir... Sir
this is Mano speaking, sir
Oh, how many of you will talk?
Okay
I sent a photo on WhatsApp...
Check if it's the old man's or not
Whose is it, huh?
Yeah... It's him, sir...
It's him
Very good
Okay
Now listen carefully to what I'm saying
The kidnapper who send this photo
called Bhanu and is negotiating
for one and a half crore
What?
One and a half crore?
That's not important right now
At 2:00 PM
They are meeting under
the parking lot of JRC Mall
You need to be there by 1:45 PM. Got it?
Okay, sir
So, what are you going to do, sir?
Listen carefully
Okay, bye
Bhanu, check if there's a signal.
- There is
Yeah, baby
Everything is safe here
First, call Bhanu and
tell him the body has arrived
I will do it right away
Hello Bhanu
Where are you?
You told me to come
at sharp 2 o'clock, right?
I've been here for a long time
Where are you?
Shouting... shouting I avoid
You only beg... no shouting
Do you brought money
money, money
I brought it
Did you bring my dad's body?
Of course
your father's body
in my vehicle
and my vehicle
under my arm
yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, hello
Hello
[Snaps fingers] Hello
Sir... Sir...
That's my car, sir.
That's mine... My car
You park your car right next to the 'No
Parking' sign in Nippu Nagaraju's circle
and casually talk on the phone?
Do you think I can't tow it?
It's not that you can't tow it, sir...
I thought it was just for a short while,
and no one would notice
There's an important
parcel in the car, sir.
I need to deliver it urgently.
Please let it go this time... Please...
I have a record of towing cars
belonging to MLAs, MPs, and Ministers.
After all, your car is no big deal
I understand your elevation, sir
Just tell me how much the fine is,
and I'll pay it
How many fines have you paid so far, kid?
I'm sincere, sir.
I haven't paid a single fine
Oh, he says he's sincere...
Check his record
Yes, sir
Do you even have machines to check?
His fines are piling up like
tail! Phew, is it over?
Tell me the total, sir.
I'll pay via Google Pay
Hello
You don't pay me
- Then...?
You'll get a message tonight
about where the car recovery point is
Go there in the morning, pay the fine,
and get your car back
You thought you'd pay a lack?
Thunder here.
What is it?
Arrogance... Sorry, I mean... thunder
That's it.
Hey bring the vehicle
Oh! Your bloody sincerity...
You messed up my whole plan!
[Cell phone rings]
Ritu
I need to see you urgently, dear
Hey, where is the body?
Come here once, I'll explain
everything in detail. Just come once
Hey fool! I'm getting tense here,
and you're asking me to come there?
Alright, stay there, I'm coming
Here, here, stop...
hey... hey... stop there...
Hey
Where is the car?
The police took it away
Shit,
the police?
But there's a body in it!
It's not that bad
just traffic police.
If we pay a fine, they'll let it go
If they find the body
then
we won't go to Goa anymore...
it'll be jail, a lifetime in prison!
Let's go, come on
- I get it
That's why I've set this up
Now, I am the body
I'll squeeze into the bag
You take this bag,
dump it there, and collect the money
After that,
I'll spray myself and come out. Got it?
Without the body...
- First, you do this.
Then we'll see... First, you get in.
I'll explain, just get in!
Careful.
Slowly.
Don't panic. Take care.
That idiot
is deliberately making me wait
No choice
we have no other option
we must wait
[Cell phone rings]
Hey MRP
what's up, you're here already?
We've been waiting
here for a long time, sir
We'll go outside,
grab some tea and come back, sir
Do one thing
there's a biryani point nearby
Go there, have some biryani and come back
Thank you, sir.
You ...
You fools...
What's going on here? What are you doing?
See
Listen carefully to what I say
until the deal is done, don't go
out of here. I'll tear you apart, idiots
Sorry, sir... we'll stay here
Remember what I said
before Bhanu comes,
you have to get rid of the body
Oh
alright, sir
Stay alert
Bloody Idiot
Okay, sir.
Put it on mute
[Cell phone rings]
Hello
Put the money in B1...
the body is in B3, go and collect it
Hey... Stop.
I think we are not doing smart work?
What do you mean?
Now
how much do you think
the dead body's weight will be?
Around 80 to 100 kg
And the weight of a bag full of money?
About 20-25 kg, why...?
So why do we need a 100 kg body?
We just need the cash, right?
Correct
What happened, sir? Where's the bag?
Forget the bag...
did you bring the dead body already?
No
we came back because we
thought we should work smart
What's this smart work?!
Instead of carrying a 100 kg body, it's
easier to carry a 25 kg money bag, sir
You idiots
there's no money in that bag.
That's a trap
Bhanu must have taken the body and gone.
You guys are done...
I'll tell you once I'm back
Sir
Stop!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
Who are you all?
I'll show you what Bhanu is about
Again they took the body
Shit
Did you catch the guy upstairs?
No, it wasn't him
it was a woman
like Lady Bruce,
she tricked me and took the bag
Damn... these thieves
took the money and still
left without giving the body
Don't worry
your cash is safe
It's all in a safe place
Shivanna and I
filled the bag with fake notes
- Fake notes?
Yes, Bhanu. I didn't like how
they were using your situation for cash.
That's why I called
the sir and talked to him
Shivanna
I need to hear one thing from you
I said no
I wanted to give you a surprise
I didn't call you to give me a surprise
I called you to catch that guy
Because of you putting in fake notes,
they took the body again
I unnecessarily got you involved
It's my mistake
leave it
Ah...
Oh...
[Singing song]
Oh god
Bundle
A big bundle
With this, I will settle
Hey
I know that this bundle has
gold
diamonds
and diamond-encrusted necklaces
All would be in this
Oh.. what's this?
The bundle is moving.. what is this?
Is it moving?
Wow.. let's talk about this...
move it aside...
take a right.. take a straight...
there seems to be a wild boar trapped
in it.. We need to deal with it today...
stop, brake.. your brake
Hey, what's this boar making
strange sounds? Oh, get a stick...
It's done...
Hit... hit...
The boar is dead.
The boar is hitting.
Bro...
Why is the boar hitting?
Will the boars also hit?
[Cell phone rings]
Ritu
I'm safe.
Did you take the money..?
- Hey Maggi
He put fake money in the bag
He tricked us
He even set the police there
I just missed it
Oh.. no.. no
oh my Goa
oh my Goa..!
It feels like hit on your heads
with a battle,
all because of my three Idiots...
Damn you...
How
how cleverly I had planned everything
Hah... Can't even do the small
tasks I told you... Again, hard work...
What' that?
Smart work... Sir...
In the pit, smart work, you fool
waste fellow
You have wasted such a brilliant plan
You fools with your buffoonery,
fools with your buffoonery
We don't know that there
is no money in the bag, sir.
If you had told us when
you changed the plan, maybe...
What would I tell you? What would
I tell you? I'll hit you with a bottle
I told you a plan
But you keep the useless
Mandakini's body safe in the fridge
But when it comes to a crore
rupees' worth body, you miss it
Useless fools
Do you know what the punishment
for the foolish, reckless work you did is?
We thought it would be
a 50-50 partnership, right?
It won't be, Master
It won't be
70-30... take that and leave
- Sir, sir... Sir
Hah... mistake, mistake
Not 70-30
It's 90
understand?
Where will I give you that 10?
There is no chance for even my 90,
where's it going? Damn you, you fools
[Inaudible]
Oh
- [Snoring]
he over drank and slept, so it's fine now
Otherwise, we could be die by his words
How did he hit us like this,
like some idiot...?
Ugh, what a fool, he hit us like this
Hey
what are you thinking about now?
Something seems not well here
This guy is up to something
I'll be back in a minute
[Line ringing]
Hello... Ammu...
What?
You said your colleague is missing, right?
Is she Mandakini..?
Yes,
Mandakini
Why, are you asking now..?
Has anyone filed a complaint
about her being missing?
Not yet
we are planning to do it tomorrow morning
Why are you
suddenly focusing on Mandakini now..?
It's nothing... I'll call you
again and explain everything clearly
Bye
Hey,
what is this?
What's the connection between
your body and the fridge?
Hey!
Give me the gun...
- Hey! Hey!
Sit down. Sit down
Answer me
What's my connection
with the body in the fridge?
Are you mentally disturbed?
If there's no connection
how did you say that the
body in the fridge is Mandakini?
Mmm...
Tell me, madam
Sir
my Bhaagi is missing, sir
It's probably gone to
the neighbor's house, madam.
It'll come back in two days
after playing around
He's not a kid sir. It's my puppy, a dog
Your dog is missing.
His buffalo was missing
I lost my mind.
What do you want me to do?
Should everyone take a
bus and go to Mental hospital?
This is a police station
not a business center
Do you understand, madam?
But I have no one else, sir
it's very close to me
Then, take it close to you
but don't send dogs out on the streets.
Do you understand?
This is what we have to do
Search for it by giving ads, madam.
I've got a lot of work to do,
don't disturb me. You just leave, madam
Shankar Goud
Sir
Is this what you call "friendly policing"?
Is this the way how you speak to girls?
Where's the respect?
I can understand your emotions
What's the name of your dog?
It's Bhaagi, sir.
one year old
Shih Tzu breed
Nice breed
Thank you, sir
Please write down your dog's
details on the paper over there Yes, sir
Damn...
If he saw a girl, he will
follow her like a street dog. Rascal
It's done, sir. I've written it down
Hot breed
Hello
Sir
you
Surprise
Wow... Bhaagi
Bhaagi...
where did you go leaving me behind?
Hey Bhaagi...
Stop
Hey you...
Hey Bhaagi
Oh come here, come here
Bhaagi...
Sir
thank you
thank you so much, Sir
I thought I missed Bhaagi,
but you brought it
Mandakini...
[Both laughing]
It's an unidentified body,
nobody knows about this body
Even though no one has filed a complaint,
you revealed its name
You said, "Add it to
the list of orphaned bodies."
You tried to pin your crime on us
your crime on us
In the end,
you turned our story into yours.
Tell me
You killed Mandakini, didn't you?
Why are you staring like an owl?
Just tell, what you have done.
[Laughs]
Nice
I expected you guys
wouldn't have much sense
There's a bit of
intelligence in your heads
If you talk like this
your brain will get smashed
Hey, what's going on
with the discussion with him?
Just kill him?
Will you tell?
Or Will you die?
Hey, why is he crying like this?
[Laughing]
Do you think I'm the kind of person
who would wet my pants looking at a gun?
Between me and Mandakini
there is a relation such
as dog and it's peel has
That dog, peel story is different
But with you and me
we have as much relation
as a bullet and a court
You are not getting it, right?
I'll explain
This...
Can you read or shall I explain?
Shoot at sight order
The ones who are hiding
the bodies from the hospital
wherever
whenever
However
as soon as they found.
To shoot and dispose them,
I've got permission letter
How can you shoot like that, sir?
- I can shoot however I want, sir
Yes
Cremation for you, promotion for me
both will happen at the same time
If I think I don't want
to take promotions and honours
I'll take your three dead bodies
and place them in front of Bhanu
He'll give me a crore
of rupees after seeing it
He was that much angry on you
So
however you look at it
you are in the danger
Oh, oh, oh
Give the gun.
Give the gun to him
Oh, what happened?
Oh, keep it down
I know you don't have a scene
to shoot or a plan to escape.
What is this?
Sorry, sir...
you take care of your business
So by evening
you'll get the old body
The money that comes from it will be mine
Make sure of that
From now on,
I won't be giving ideas, got it?
Okay, sir
If you bring me the body,
you'll stay alive
If not, what will happen?
You'll turn into dead bodies yourselves
Okay, sir
Remember
by evening.
- Okay, sir
Ugh, you
Ugh, damn it
Even the gun is in our
hands also he made us sweat
[Cell phone rings]
Daivaji
Oh God... this is what
"Between a rock and a hard place"
First, answer the call
Hello, Sir
Hey Mano
You three guys come to my home once
Hey
That's...
the money hasn't been arranged yet
We need to talk about that arrangement
Start immediately
Hey
Whether we go or not,
definitely we would die.
Ugh
Damn it
Hey Janaki
where's brother?
Just wait for two minutes
Why did he even call me here?
His height and expression make no sense
Bloody fellow
- [Phone chimes]
78,460 rupees
- What's that?
The car challan amount
We need to pay up and bring the body
What else can we do with that body now
That Bhanu screwed us over completely,
didn't he?
Ugh.. Isn't it?
What a mess
Now what?
This wretched guy is here too
This magnet guy is also here, huh?
These MRP guys still
haven't gone to Somalia?
What is he doing here?
Brother, did you called us?
My father's body is out there somewhere
What do you mean the body is out there?
They say the body went
missing from the hospital
Don't know, who took it
That Bhanu guy is running
around the streets like a mad dog
You need to bring me that body
If you do
I will waive your fifty lakhs debt.
You've been saying you want
to settle in Goa for ages, right?
Yes, brother
Bring me the body
and I'll make that dream come true
Okay
Yes
whoever brings the body first
the offer is only for them
[Cheering]
[Music]
"I thought, why not?"
"But I fell flat on my face"
"We joined forces"
"We'll win soon"
"For the MRP price"
"We searched the whole town"
"The rate seemed good"
"But the luck wasn't great"
"We've sunk in completely,"
"What else is left to lose?"
"Struggles with life itself"
"All for a penny"
"What's a swallowing anaconda to us?"
"We are like a moving Golconda"
"Relentless struggles"
"All for a penny"
"Running and racing"
"Can't be avoided,
can't be avoided, can't be avoided"
"For life's survival!"
"Who is less than whom?"
"No one is less,
no one is less, no one is less"
"All for money"
[Music]
I kept saying no, no from the beginning,
You dragged this business disaster
all the way here. No one listened to me
Hey... we still haven't found that corpse,
man. We have to go abroad.
If we stick around with you,
we'll end up dead either at the
hands of that CI guy or Bhanu
Before they kill us, we'll
probably die from BP and sugar levels
because of all the
stress this guy is causing
Hey, stop it, guys
Let's think of something
If Mano is here, there's always a plan.
Oh, a salute to you, man
If Mano is here, there's a plan...
and if we follow it
there's disaster too
That's not, dude
- Hey, don't talk, man
Just shut up
Yes, man
Listening to his nonsense
got us a "shoot on sight" order
Pammu
even you too?
Aren't my life and breath valuable?
Come on, let's go find that body ourselves
Pammu
what about me?
Sit with that corpse in the fridge
and keep saying,
"If Mano is here, there's a plan,"
and talk to yourself
- Hey, what are you talking to him, man?
Hello
Sir, this is Shivaji speaking
from Banjara Hills Traffic PS
Tell me, Shivaji
Yesterday
we brought in a car from a towing service
When we opened the trunk because
of a strange smell coming from it
we found a dead body, sir
Alright, I'll come immediately
Good morning, Sir.
The ball has landed in my court
What do you mean, Sir?
Yes... Regarding an important case
this is crucial evidence
I am taking this car
- Okay, Sir
Shivaji
- Yes, Sir
Until I say
Don't file any more cases on this body
- Okay, Sir
"Go" means all troubles go
and "va" means all pleasures come
Darling
shall I call the broker
and confirm the sea-view villa?
First, finish the job
Why the tension, babe?
We'll go there,
make our payment, and take our car
Our car
someone is stealing our car!
Shit
That CI Vishwaroopam guy
He is the one who planned
to catch us in the cellar on that day
- You mean he found the body in the car?
- Maybe
Damn it, oh my Goa...
Follow, follow, follow!
Hey, hey, hey... Stop the vehicle
there's a big bundle over there
Hey, you brainless fool
we came here to look for a body,
not trash and debris
Oh really?
Then do you have any plan?
Tell me where we are
dragging this cart to?
To the cemetery, man
We need to find the body there.
If not, we might as well dig
a grave and jump into it ourselves
I told you
from the beginning that
I wouldn't join in on this.
Yet, you guys pulled me into it
I wasn't the one planning
from the start, right?
Hey, hey, hey
That CI is driving away with a magnet car
Why is he taking his car?
Hey, did you see that?
It's Magnet and Ritu, man!
Why are they chasing their own car?
Who knows, man?
Get in!
Come on, come on
[Cell phone rings]
Hello
If you want your father's dead body
bring two crores
Hey, you scoundrels
who do you think you are?
First one crore,
then one and a half, and now two crores
Are you playing with me?
Hey! Enough shouting
Do you want your father's
dead body or not? Just say yes or no
How do I know you really have the body?
Don't waste time asking
for proofs and evidence
I'll deliver the body directly to you
Bring two crores immediately
to the under-construction KR Towers
Yes
Shivanna...
Hurry up and go!
Oh no
that fire again
Our misfortune is back
What are you waiting for?
check it
Okay, sir
RC... license... pollution...
- Hey! Stop!
Do you even know who I am?
I don't want to know about anyone,
except our fire sir.
I am CI Vishwaroopan
I'm in an urgent task,
Clear the road first.
You give a side
What dear?
Everyone keeps saying that,
they know the CI
But you are acting like CI
I'll send you to Jail. Show the papers.
It's not my own car.
Yeah! I understood now
by looking at your face,
it's clear that this car is not yours,
you must have taken it from somewhere else
Get out of the car.
Look, I'm in an urgent task.
Tell me what you need, and I'll transfer
the money, but don't irritate me like this
Shut up
I'm not irritating you
Hey! Murali
take the car's keys
Okay, sir
- Get out of the car
Hey!
- Get out
Murali, seize the car
- Okay, sir
Sir, Sir
please don't seize the car.
This car is ours
You find us for a traffic violation.
Do you remember, sir?
I can't forget your face
It's a pan-India level fraud
- Your kindness sir
Oh, you bloody burglar
You!
What have you done?
You hit me in my stomach and escaped
Who is he? Is he you partner?
You should arrest him, not me!
What man, you are passing orders to me?
You still haven't come
out of your character
You made a mistake by
giving a character to him
It's a pure lie, sir
This guy is a big thief
I paid the fine and tried to get the car
but he took it away
from the recovery place
I'll believe that, because I am a fool
But he is fire
Well said
Your kindness, sir
Hey, don't do any extra drama
I know what's in the boot
What's inside?
Is there any gold?
Well said.
There's no gold or silver
I'll tell you
there's a body in the boot
there's a dead body
It went missing two days ago
and it's in this car
This car belongs to him
Now he is in front of me
Now, You should arrest him
Does he watch web series a lot?
So, It was Magnet and
Ritu who took the body.
This shit faced lady is
following up from the hospital
Hey, call Mano
Why did you call me?
Hey
Listen carefully
Those who took the body is none other than
Magnet and Ritu
Really?
But the body is with CI now
Send the location urgently
These two are part of a
mafia that steals dead bodies, sir
Mafia?
Sir, you saw it, right?
First, he said me then us
then he said car
then about the body,
and then diverted it into the mafia
What a diversion! Hatts off!
Who's diverting?
Fire,
if you want check the boot
and see whether the body is there or not
Do you know who you're dealing with?
Fire Nagaraju
You are giving keys to him
like you are giving to a valet parking
It's Pathetic
Sir, you carry on, I'll handle it
No, he's asking something. Open the boot
Just open it once
Yes
I think you have a lot to do
He'll be satisfied. Just open it once
Yes
It's a silly case, sir.
Just some trash or something
Open it once
Yeah
Super
Do it
Open it man
Ah, Do it
[Car alarm chirps]
[Laughing]
[Coughing]
How nice it is to holding
from the front side!
He stole the car in the gap
Wow
Ritu
It wasn't me, it was Fire.
Whoever you see, will you hold them?
I am so sorry
- Baby!
May be she got confused
It's okay, you caught him from front,
that's why it's fine.
If you had caught him from the back,
- It would have been really painful
Exactly. Come on, let's catch them
Hey! Wait
we need to check how
many challans are on this car
You already took a hug, sir.
It'll balance out
A hug is a hug
Duty is duty
Check it next time, sir
- No way
Hey
let's close the deal quickly
I'll send the body up in the first lift.
You send the cash from the second lift
If you plan to put
any fake currency, then...
I won't do it like you
Like me!
What do you know about me?
- I know you are the CI Vishwaroop
But I don't have time to argue with you
How did the he get to know?
Damn these brown pants
Oh no
Hey...
Be careful
Dad
Haha...
My daddy's dead body
Daddy's body
Where did you pick him up from, man?
I found it
I found the body before that Bhanu found
[Laughs]
"We ran the whole city for MRP"
"The rate is good but fate is bad"
"We are already drowning in it.
We have nothing to lose now"
"We will risk our lives for money"
"Our throats work like anacondas"
"All this struggle is for money"
"You need to hustle and bustle"
"You need to do it for your life"
"Nobody will back down here"
"It is for money"
Ugh... What's this at this time?
- Is this for mosquitos to die or humans?
- Hey
It's me
Poor guy,
he's trying to shoo away the flies
Oh no... what is this!?
You fool Alright, let' go.
Ugh, I'm unable to sit. Move.
This dog is sitting on half the seat!
Shabash, Mano!
Finally, you've got it
Daivaji is completely happy
My heart is content now
If you could do something about the loan
waiver, we too would happily head home
When Daivaji says something,
it's a promise
Janaki
- Oh, brother
"We will risk our lives for money"
"Our throats work like anacondas"
"All this struggle is for money"
Happy now?
You have one more task to do, though
Sir,
what task, sir?
You bloody burglar
Hey, you're back again!
Yes
after a lot of effort and struggles,
we've come up with a plan
at the climax,
you entered to take the money
This money is ours
leave the bag here
go straight, take a left, and head home
Looking at you, it makes me feel sorry
Why should I bother with your struggles?
I'll give you 5 lakh rupee
take it and get married, settle down
Thanks for noticing our struggle
but what's the point of your charity?
You're offering 5 lakh
I'll give you 10 lakh,
leave the bag and go.
Hey
stop bothering me
not 10, not 15
I'll give you 20 lakh
Go have a celebration
What's the bargain with you?
You are a fool
If I hit you on the head with this...
you know, we can't even do
a postmortem on your body.
What's this..?
you're over acting while
I am taking it as easy
What are you arguing with him about?
Hey, hey
- Just bring it here
Don't you remember a policeman has a gun?
You leave here with rods in hand
one bullet is enough to knock both of
you down. - Let's sit and talk things out
Sit down... sit... sit down
Why is he coming?
- Let's go. Come
- Hey
Hey... Hey...
Hey...
Are you playing games with me,
saying that you will give my father body?
You want to take the money
without my father's body?
- I'll kill you one by one
- Maggi
Leave it... leave it
leave...
- This is mine
- Leave
Leave it
- Leave it
You stay here until
my father's body is found
Slowly. Please, she will get pain.
Hey, where is my father's body?
That idiot,
put it in the car and took it away
That's the body? It was sent upstairs
Hey... that's not my father's body
Is it?
Then, Is it Mandakini's body?
How many bodies do you have with you?
What are you selling in your shop?
You fool
[Phone ringing]
That Bhanu attacked on me multiple times
Do you know why I left him?
Dad
Look at this
Hey Hey Hey
Release us and go.
Hey
Cry and cry...
he should die
Then
Then only, I'll get the real happiness
Now I've got the chance
No brother
It's not right to do that to your father
I'm doing whatever final
ritual I want to do to my father
There's a huge difference between
doing final ritual and burning it
Hey
Remove your hand.
Please, brother
- Remove your hand
Hey hey...
Please, brother... please
Brother... please brother... don't do that
Sir, sir, no sir
Please, brother
Brother, please... stop it, please
Hey.
Brother
Hey, It's a great sin.
How dare you to touch me?
- Sorry, sorry
Leave us
Hey
No, brother...
Brother please brother...
Tie them up
No, brother
Brother
Hey.
Coming, Coming, it's here, It's Over
Hey, next untie me... come on
You fraud.
You should take off your clothes,
not your ties, for the mess you made.
You are the worst fellow in the world.
- Get lost
Okay, okay
- Hey, untie me
Hey
Escape
Go away
You
Hey, hold on, lift him
Hit him... hit him
How much are you tortured us?
[Screaming in pain]
Shivanna
Yes, tell me, Bhanu?
Tie him up
Alright
there are already two bundles in the car
Throw him with those as well. Okay
You both helped me twice
with my father's issue
Thank you
In the future, if you have any problems
Don't forget that I'm here for you
Okay, sure
If they find out that we did all this
What's the matter?
He'll make three more bundles ready.
Oh no, let's build
up our image as good people
So
aren't we good people?
[Crying]
For the past 3 days,
you haven't spoken a word to me
Does this mean I won't help you...?
- Ammu... Ammu... please
Don't start this again
I'll do whatever you say
But, I need a business
plan in another 6 months
By the way, when did you buy this dog?
It's Mandakini's pet
Bhaagi
Yes, Mandakini. That reminds me
What's up with that CI guy? When I asked
him about his connection with Mandakini
He said it's a dog and peel relation
Bhaagi Darling
Do you know anything?
Do you know?
If you do, tell me
Just because you got married,
do you think I will leave you?
May be you maintained it secretly
I have already told everyone
if you do anything to me
No no
even if something happens
to me unexpectedly
it all comes to you only
Ugh
when you never intended to marry
Why did you behave like
this with me... aah...
Mandakini
Hey. Mandu
If I say you died due to an accident,
who will believe it?
I am finish
I've had doubts on CI
about this from the beginning
Amrita came and filed
a missing case about Mandakini
When that happened,
my suspicion grew even more
For some reason,
I thought it was better
to do a secret inquiry
The culprit was caught
In this case, A1 is the CI
A2 is the Magnet
A3 is Ritu
I still can't figure
out what happened to them
Hey
don't worry
In this case, you three aren't criminals
you're just witnesses
To tell it clearly, you're victims
Thank you, sir
The story that started with you
ended with you
Oh, no need to thank me
At least now, do your work properly...
or else, will people get involved
in some shady business again?
Whatever you do
do it happily. OK?
Go now
- We will leave, sir
We'll leave, Shankar
- Bye, sir.
Funny fellow
Hey...
- Hey...
Can you get me a tea or coffee?
Can you get me a Beer or Brandy?
Sreenu
- Sreenu
- Giri
- Hey
Hey
Do you know them?
Do you know him?
I am the CI of this station.
I am the thief of this station
Hey,
what he's saying is true
He's the CI of this station
but today he just finished dealing
with dead bodies and fell into the gutter
Hey hey hey
So, we're both exactly
the same kind of thieves. Hey...